{"name":"M21_03_Operatoren","currentQuestionIndex":-1,"questionList":[{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole aus für folgenden Code:\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tint i = 0;\n\t\tint j = i++ + ++i;\n\t\tSystem.out.println( j );\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":1,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"4","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tint i = 0;\n\t\tint j = ++i + i++;\n\t\tSystem.out.println( j );\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":150,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":3,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"4","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tint i = 100;\n\t\tint j = 10;\n\t\tSystem.out.println( i%j );\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":3,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"10","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tint i = 0;\n\t\tint j = 1;\n\t\tif(!i && j)\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(\"1\");\n\t\telse\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(\"2\");\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tboolean b1 = true, b2 = false, b3 = true;\n\t\tSystem.out.println( b1&&b2&&!b3 );\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":3,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tint i = 10, j = 12, k = 1;\n\t\tk += i++ - --j;\n\t\tSystem.out.println(k);\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"-2","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"-1","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tint i = 10;\n\t\ti++;i++;++i;\n\t\tint j = i++;\n\t\tSystem.out.println(j);\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"11","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"13","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"14","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tbyte b1 = 2;\n\t\tb1 = b1 + 10;\n\t\t\n\t\tbyte b2 = 2;\n\t\tb2 += 10;\n\t\t\n\t\tSystem.out.println(b1 + \" \" + b2);\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"10 12","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"12 12","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"12 10","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"MultipleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tint i = 19;\n\t\tint j = -5;\n\t\tSystem.out.println( i%j );\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"4","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"-4","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"-3","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"MultipleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tint i = -21;\n\t\tint j = 4;\t\t\n\t\tSystem.out.println( i%j );\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"-1","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"-5","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\t\n\t\tlong l1 = 30000;\n\t\tlong l2 = 10000;\n\t\t\n\t\tshort s = 0;\n\t\t\n\t\ts += l1 + l2;\n\t\tSystem.out.println(s);\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"-25536","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"40000","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error, cannot convert long to short","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\nclass One{\t\n}\n\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tstatic One one;\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tSystem.out.println(one instanceof One);\t\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"NullPointerException","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Welche der folgenden Anweisung wird **true** auf der Konsole ausgeben bei Zeile 14.\n```\ninterface Inter{}\nclass One{}\nclass Two extends One{}\nclass Three extends Two implements Inter{}\n\npublic class Test{\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\t\n\t\tOne one = new Two();\n\t\tTwo two = new Three();\n\t\tThree three = new Three();\n\t\tInter i = new Three();\n\t\t\n\t\t//your code here\n\t\t\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"System.out.print( one instanceof One);","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"System.out.print( one instanceof Two ); ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"System.out.print( two instanceof One ); ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"System.out.print( i instanceof Inter ); ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"System.out.print( i instanceof One );","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"System.out.print( three instanceof Inter );","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" System.out.print( three instanceof Two ); ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"System.out.print( three instanceof One ); ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"All of the above ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tlong l = 20;\n\t\tSystem.out.println(l instanceof Object);\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tint i = 0;\n\t\tif( i = 0 )\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(true);\n\t\telse\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(false);\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tint i = 10;\n\t\tif( i =< 15.5 )\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(true);\n\t\telse\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(false);\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"MultipleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tint i = 0, j = 1;\n\t\tif( i && j )\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(1);\n\t\telse\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(2);\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tfloat[] f = {1.3f, 1.4f, 1.5f};\n\t\tSystem.out.println( f instanceof Object );\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tint i = 10;\n\t\tint j = 20;\n\t\t\n\t\tif( i + j < 15 & i++ > 10 )\n\t\t\tSystem.out.print(i);\n\t\telse\n\t\t\tSystem.out.print(i);\n\t\t\n\t\tint x = 10;\n\t\tint y = 20;\n\n\t\tif( x + y < 15 && x++ > 10 )\n\t\t\tSystem.out.print(x);\n\t\telse\n\t\t\tSystem.out.print(x);\n\n\t}\t\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"1011","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"1110","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"1010","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"1111","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt die Konsole für folgenden Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\t\t\t\n\t\t\n\t\tint i = 1;\n\t\tint j = 2;\n\t\t\n\t\tint k = i + 10 * i++ - j * 5 + --j;\n\t\tSystem.out.println(k);\n\t}\t\n}\n```","timer":300,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"47","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"46","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"7","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\nint x = 5;\n\nint y = 6\n\nint z = 50;\n\nSystem.out.println(x + y + z);\n```\n\nWhat will be the output?","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"61","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"66","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"5650","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"x+y+z","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\nint sum1 = 100 + 50;\n\nint sum2 = sum1 + 250;\n\nint sum3 = sum2 + sum2;\n\nSystem.out.println(sum3);\n```","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"950","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"800","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"sum2sum2","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"sum1250","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Which of the following is assignment operator?","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"==","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"=","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"=+","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"++","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\nint x = 10;\n\nx = x + 5;\n\nSystem.out.println(x);\n```","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"15","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"55","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"x5","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"x /= 3\n\n\nWhich of the below statements matches with above statement?","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"x = 3/x","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"x/3","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"x=x/3","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"x/x=3","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\nint x = 4;\n\nSystem.out.println(x < 5 && x < 10);\n```\n\nWhat will be the output?","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"4","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"x<4 && x<10","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\nint x = 4.4;\n\nint y = 5.5;\n\nSystem.out.println(x == y);\n```\n\nWhat will be the output?","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"4.4","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"5.5","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What is the output of below code?\n\n```\nint x = 5;\n\nSystem.out.println(x++);\n\nSystem.out.println(x);\n```","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"5 5","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"5 6","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"6 6","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"6 5","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What will be the output of the following program?\n\n```\npublic class Main {\n    public static void main(String[] args) {\n        System.out.print(-83.0/0);\n    }\n}\n```","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"infinity","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"compile-time error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"-infinity","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"__________ operator increases the value of the operand by 1.","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"--","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"-","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"++","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"+","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"if p=10, then the output of the expression c= p++ *5 is","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"50","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"55","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"45","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"if a = 30, then value of b = a--+--a","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"56","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"58","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"57","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"59","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"The output of the following statements will be\n\nint a = 14; b= 4;\n\nboolean x=(a>b)? true:false","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"none of the above","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"The return value of relational expressions and logical expressions is ________","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"integer value","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"decimal value","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean value","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"none of the above","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"&& operator will return true value only if both the relational expressions involved returns the value ","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"both","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"none of the above","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"In this expression the ________ logical operator that will be performed first _\n\n((a>b)&&(b>c))||(b>a)!(c>b))","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"&&","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"||","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"!","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"?","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"The return value of the expression\n\n10<15 || 2>3||100>23 will be","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"False","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"True","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Yes","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"No","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What values do a and b hold after the following expressions?\n\nint a = 5; int b = 10; b = a++;\n\n\n","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"a = 5 and b = 5;","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"a = 5 and b = 6","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"a = 6 and b = 5","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"a = 6 and b = 6","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What value does b hold after the following expressions?\n\nint b = 5; b = b % 2;?","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"compiler error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What value does b hold after the following expressions?\n\nint b = 7; b = 22 / b;","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"compiler error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"3.33","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Can the result of a modulus calculation be 0?","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"yes","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"no","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What value does b hold after the following expressions?\n\nbyte a = 1;byte b = ++a;","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"compiiler error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What values do a and b hold after the following expressions?\n\n```\nboolean a = true;boolean b = false;\nif (a | b) {System.out.println(true);}\n```","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"compiler error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What symbol do we use for XOR (exclusive OR)?","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"&","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"^","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"!","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"|","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What symbol do we use for NOT?","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"&","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"^","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"!","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"|","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What is the result of a logical operator?","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"int","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"char","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"long","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt folgender Code aus?\n```\nclass Test {\n    public static void main(String args[])  {\n       System.out.println(10  +  20 + \"GeeksQuiz\"); \n       System.out.println(\"GeeksQuiz\" + 10 + 20); \n   }  \n}\n```\n\nA.\n30GeeksQuiz\nGeeksQuiz30\n\nB. \n1020GeeksQuiz\nGeeksQuiz1020\n\nC. \n30GeeksQuiz\nGeeksQuiz1020\n\nD. \n1020GeeksQuiz\nGeeksQuiz30","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"A","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"B","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"C","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"D","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt folgender Code aus?\n```\nclass Test {\n    public static void main(String args[])  {\n       System.out.println(10*20 + \"GeeksQuiz\");\n       System.out.println(\"GeeksQuiz\" + 10*20);\n   } \n}\n```\nA.\n10*20GeeksQuiz\nGeeksQuiz10*20\n\nB.\n200GeeksQuiz\nGeeksQuiz200\n\nC.\n200GeeksQuiz\nGeeksQuiz10*20\n\nD.\n1020GeeksQuiz\nGeeksQuiz220","timer":30,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"A","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"B","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"C","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"D","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"}],"sessionConfig":{"theme":"Material","readingConfirmationEnabled":false,"showResponseProgress":true,"confidenceSliderEnabled":false,"music":{"enabled":{"lobby":true,"countdownRunning":true,"countdownEnd":true},"shared":{"lobby":false,"countdownRunning":false,"countdownEnd":false},"volumeConfig":{"global":60,"lobby":60,"countdownRunning":60,"countdownEnd":60,"useGlobalVolume":true},"titleConfig":{"lobby":"Song3","countdownRunning":"Song1","countdownEnd":"Song1"}},"nicks":{"memberGroups":[],"maxMembersPerGroup":10,"autoJoinToGroup":false,"selectedNicks":[],"blockIllegalNicks":true}},"state":"Inactive","currentStartTimestamp":-1}